The earliest known academic rating about the meaning of random was by John Venn
已知最早的是 John Venn 于 1888 年在他的著作 The Logic of Chance
in 1888 and his book called the logic of chance. He said, Perhaps the best
对随机这一概念进行学术定义 他认为
typical example that we can give of the scientific meaning of random
也许关于随机分布的科学定义的
distribution is afforded by the arrangement of the drops of rain in a shower. No
最典型的例子是一场雨中雨滴落下的位置分布 没有
one can give a guess whereabouts at any instant a drop will fall, but we know
人能够预测在任何瞬间一滴雨会落在哪里 但是我们知道
that if we put out a sheet of paper it will gradually become uniformly spotted
如果我们放一张纸 这张纸就会渐渐均匀的淋上雨滴
over. And if we were to mark out any two equal areas on the paper, these would
并且如果我们在纸上任意全出两块区域 通常这两块区域会
gradually tend to be struck equally often. Therefore, when we have a random
渐渐平均的淋上雨 因此 当我们有一个随机
sample, each subject has an equal chance of being selected. And then our sample
样本 其中每一个对象都有均等的机会被挑选到时 我们的样本
is more likely to approximate the population.
更有可能估计总体